Guide to the J. B. Fuqua Papers, 1929-2006 and undated RL.00426
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession 2008-0024
  - Home Office Files
    - Venard, Torbet & McConnell, KTVE TV Folder - Correspondence and other materials regarding Radio and TV station (Sales) Rep company that serviced KTVE for a time, 1963-1965 (Box 77)
    - W - Miscellaneous Folder - Assorted Correspondence and other materials, 1962-1965 (Box 77)
      July 17, 1962, Letter from Thomas Hennesy to Ray Carrow regarding racial tensions/troubles in Augusta with an attached speech.
    - Speech Material (#1) Folder - Assorted Speeches, talking notes, publications, reports, and other materials, 1961-1964 (Box 77)
    - WGAC Folder - Assorted materials regarding WGAC (Radio) [note: found inside Speech Material (#1) folder), 1946-1959 (Box 77)
    - 6 sets of cards containing notes (Box 77)
    - Speech Material (#2) Folder - Assorted Speeches, publications, reports, and other materials, 1959-1964 (Box 78)
    - Speech Material (#3) Folder - Assorted Speeches, publications, reports, and other materials, 1959-1963 (Box 78)
    - Speech Material (#4) Folder - Assorted Speeches, publications, reports, and other materials, 1957-1961 (Box 78)
    - FCC Rentavision of Brunswick, Inc. Folder - Correspondence and materials regarding Rentavision, particularly those related to FCC concern, 1966-1972 (Box 79)
    - CATV - Financial Reports, Operating Reports, Proposed Fees Folder - Correspondence and materials regarding Cablevision of Augusta, particularly those related to FCC concern, 1970-1972 (Box 79)
    - Rentavision of Brunswick - Minutes of Board Meetings, 1968-1972 (Box 79)
    - Rentavision of Bunswick, Inc. Report Fiscal Year 6-30-1972 Folder - Fiscal year report and associated correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 79)
    - CATV Insurance, Brunswick Augusta Folder - Assorted Correspondence And Materials regarding Insurance for Rentavision, 1971-1972 (Box 79)
    - Rentavision of Brunswick, Inc. License Agreement… Southern Bell Folder - Correspondence & Materials regarding establishing phone wire delivery of TV, 1971-1972 (Box 79)
    - Rentavision Franchise Ordinance Folder - Correspondence and Materials regarding the granting and transfer of franchise to CATV/Cablevision/Rentavision, 1965-1971 (Box 79)
    - CATV Proposed Rules 8/5/71 Folder - Corresp, publications, materials related to establishment of rules for CATV, 1971-1972 (Box 79)
    - CATV Rentavision of Burnswick, Inc. Folder - Correspondence, Reports, and other materials regarding Rentavision (Box 79)
    - Investments - Timber Folder - Reports, Correspondence, publications, and other materials regarding Timber Companies, 1964-1966 (Box 79)
    - Georgia Power Co. Folder - Reports, Correspondence, and other materials regarding Georgia Power Co. (Note: Fuqua built a building for and leased it to GPC), 1965-1966 (Box 79)
    - Western Stoneware Financial Statements Folder - Reports, Correspondence, publication, and other materials regarding Western Stoneware, 1965-1967 (Box 80)
    - Great Lakes Western Stoneware Binder - Reports, ledger, correspondence, and other materials regarding Great Lakes Industries, 1961-1966 (Box 80)
    - Correspondence to Mrs. W. H. Cato from J.B. Fuqua regarding Willingham Finance Co. and Liabilities he had to her, 1957 (Box 80)
      This letter details his thinking about his finance ventures. Letter found alone in box.
    - Fuqua Industries, Inc. Folder - an outline of business expansion program for FI for Sherman Drawdy of Georgia Railroad Bank and Trust Co., 1965 (Box 80)
    - Unidentified Green Folder - appraisal Report TV Properties owned by Fuqua Industries, Inc. (Box 80)
    - Western Stoneware Folder - Correspondence, Reports, advertising pamphlets, and other materials regarding Western Stoneware, 1965-1967 (Box 80)
    - Great Lakes Industries Folder - Correspondence, Court transcript and other documents regarding an action brought against Great Lakes Industries, 1965-1966 (Box 80)
    - Statement Western Stoneware Division and Consolidated Statement Great Lakes Industries, Inc., March 1967 (Box 80)
    - Statement Western Stoneware Division and Consolidated Statement Great Lakes Industries, Inc., April 22 1967 (Box 80)
    - Western Stoneware Company Cash & Sales Report Folder - Two (2) Sales and Cash Reports, 1967 (Box 80)
    - James E. Covington Folder - Correspondence from Thomas Hennessy to James Covington regarding Western Stoneware, 1966-1967 (Box 80)
    - Western Stoneware Consultant's Report Folder, 1967 (Box 80)
    - Great Lakes Industries: General File Folder - Correspondence, reports and other materials regarding Great Lakes Industries, 1963-1967 (Box 80)
    - Advertising Research Foundation SPECIAL TWO DAY STUDY THE CONTINUING STUDY of NEWSPAPER READING Study # 88 and 89, 1945 (Box 80)
    - VISUAL ELECTRONICS CORPORATION PRICE LIST (EFFECTIVE: February 15, 1965) (Box 80)
    - Advertising Research Foundation THE CONTINUING STUDY of NEWSPAPER READING Study # 118, 1948 (Box 80)
    - Advertising Research Foundation THE CONTINUING STUDY of NEWSPAPER READING Study # 116, 1948 (Box 80)
    - Four (4) copies of Financial Statement for GEORGIA CAROLINA BROADCASTING COMPANY AUGUSTA, GEORGIA JULY 1, 1962 THROUGH JANUARY 31, 1963 (Box 81)
    - Ten (10) copies of Balance Sheet Statement for GEORGIA CAROLINA BROADCASTING COMPANY AUGUSTA, GEORGIA JUNE 30, 1962 (Box 81)
    - Eight (8) copies of Audit for GEORGIA CAROLINA BROADCASTING COMPANY AUGUSTA, GEORGIA JUNE 30, 1962 (Box 81)
    - Nine (9) copies of human relations commission 1972 ANNUAL REPORT UNDERSTANDING THROUGH COMMUNICATION, 1972 (Box 81)
    - Two (2) copies of Balance Sheet Statement for GEORGIA CAROLINA BROADCASTING COMPANY AUGUSTA, GEORGIA JUNE 30, 1963 (Box 81)
    - Balance Sheet Statement for FUQUA INDUSTRIES, INC., AND SUBSIDIARIES JUNE 30, 1966 (Box 81)
    - Seven (7) copies of Audit for FUQUA INDUSTRIES, INC. AUGUSTA, GEORGIA JUNE 30, 1965 (Box 81)
    - Balance Sheet Statement for FUQUA INDUSTRIES, INC. AUGUSTA, GEORGIA JUNE 30, 1965 (Box 81)
    - Twelve (12) copies of Balance Sheet Statement for FUQUA INDUSTRIES, INC. AUGUSTA, GEORGIA JUNE 30, 1964 (Box 81)
    - Balance Sheet Statement for FUQUA INDUSTRIES, INC. AUGUSTA, GEORGIA JUNE 30, 1966, 1966 (Box 81)
    - GEORGIA INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY LAMINATED WOOD MEMBERS: A MANUFACTURING POSSIBILITY FOR THE COOSA VALLEY AREA Report, 1964 (Box 81)
    - GEORGIA INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY HARDWOOD DIMENSION STOCK: A MANUFACTURING OPPORTUNITY IN GEORGIA Report, 1965 (Box 81)
    - GEORGIA INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY The Advantages of Manufacturing Asphalt and Vinyl Asbestos Floor Tile in Savannah Report, 1965 (Box 81)
    - GEORGIA INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY SOURCES OF CAPITAL FOR GEORGIA BUSINESS AND INDUSTRY Report, 1965 (Box 81)
    - GEORGIA INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY EASTERN WHITE PINE: TIMBER RESOURCES, UTILIZATION, AND MARKET OUTLETS IN THE SOUTHERN APPALACHIAN AREA Report, 1965 (Box 81)
    - GEORGIA INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY The Feasibility of Producing LAMINATED HARDWOOD DECKING In Georgia Report, 1966 (Box 81)
    - Three (3) copies of Stormor advertising pamphlet book (Box 81)
    - Reprint of WHAT IS MANAGEMENT? article from MANUAL OF EXCELLENT MANAGEMENT (5th Edition), 1959 (Box 81)
    - Reprint of What Makes Them Excellent? article from MANUAL OF EXCELLENT MANAGEMENT (9th Edition), 1965 (Box 81)
    - Reprint of Is This Bank Excellently Managed? article from The Bankers Magazine (Vol. 148, No. 4), 1965 (Box 81)
    - Three (3) copies of reprint of Building a free-form conglomerate article from Business Week (February 10, 1968) (Box 81)
    - Bank of New York Folder - Correspondence to/from Bank of New York, 1965-1967 (Box 81)
    - Unidentified Leather notebook- Outline of Program for Office Building at 10th and Reynolds Street, Augusta, Georgia and associated correspondence and materials, 1966-1969 (Box 81)
    - Insurance Folder - Publications, reports, correspondence and materials regarding Insurance, 1956-1960 (Box 81)
    - Great Southern Real Estate Trust Balance Sheet report of the Great Southern RE Trust, 9/30/1966 (Box 81)
    - W. E. Long Folder - Correspondence from The W. E. Long Co. Co-op Bakery Man. Services, 1963 (Box 81)
    - Three (3) copies of Exhibit and Schedules for the GEORGIA CAROLINA BROADCASTING COMPANY PROFIT SHARING RETIREMENT TRUST JUNE 30, 1961 (Box 82)
    - Three (3) copies of Audit of GEORGIA CAROLINA BROADCASTING COMPANY AUGUSTA, GEORGIA JUNE 30, 1961 (Box 82)
    - Five (5) copies of Balance Sheet Statement for GEORGIA CAROLINA BROADCASTING COMPANY AUGUSTA, GEORGIA JUNE 30, 1961 (Box 82)
    - Three (3) copies of Balance Sheet Statement for GEORGIA CAROLINA BROADCASTING COMPANY AUGUSTA, GEORGIA JUNE 30, 1960 (Box 82)
    - Two (2) copies of Audit of GEORGIA CAROLINA BROADCASTING COMPANY AUGUSTA, GEORGIA JUNE 30, 1960, 1960 (Box 82)
    - AUGUSTA/RICHMOND COUNTY HUMAN RELATIONS COMMISSION POLICY & PROCEDURE MANUAL Adopted May 1975 (Box 82)
    - Unidentified yellow envelope containing (often multiple copies of) publications, Fuqua's Resume, and other materials most of which is related to Natco Corporation, 1966-1967 (Box 82)
    - Imperial 400 Motels information booklet, 1965 (Box 82)
    - NBC informational report Close-up on Color Television (Box 82)
    - 1965 INDUSTRIAL SURVEY of GEORGIA from the Georgia State Chamber of Commerce, 1965 (Box 82)
    - New York Times Business and Finance Section for Sunday, August 25, 1968 (Box 82)
    - GEORGIA INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY MOBILE HOMES IN GEORGIA Report, 1965 (Box 82)
    - Two (2) copies of GEORGIA INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY GEORGIA'S MINERAL RESOURCES Report, 1962 (Box 82)
      Business card of Ross W. Hammond of the Georgia Institute of Technology and Index of reports attached to one copy.
    - GEORGIA INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY The Coosa Valley's Resources for the Manufacture of Wood Household Furniture Report, 1965 (Box 82)
    - GEORGIA INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY WOOD HOUSEHOLD FURNITURE: regarding A Manufacturing Possibility for Elbert County, Georgia Report, 1965 (Box 82)
    - GEORGIA INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY INVESTMENT CASTING: A Manufacturing Possibility for Elberton, Georgia Report, 1965 (Box 82)
    - Two (2) copies of Atlanta (Pub of the Atlanta Chamber of Commerce), May 1968, Article on J.B. Fuqua, p. 22 (Box 82)
    - ADAM YOUNG, INC. Folder - Contracts and correspondence between Fuqua and Young regarding Young's company representing Fuqua in selling time and services on one of more of Fuqua TV stations, 1965-1966 (Box 83)
    - Federal Trade Commission Folder - Correspondence, publications, etc. regarding the FTC's prohibiting of advertisements deemed to misrepresent products, 1958-1963 (Box 83)
    - Lansing Radio Station Folder - Correspondence and other materials regarding potential purchase of radio station under construction in Lansing, Michigan, 1958-1961 (Box 83)
    - Two (2) copies of SPECIFICATIONS FOR OFFICES & STUDIO FOR WJBF (Box 83)
    - Copy of LETTER OF TRANSMITTAL of stock of The Woodman Company for/signed by Dorothy Fuqua, 1969 (Box 83)
    - STOCK PAPERS Folder - Blueprints for Offices & Studio WJBF, 1957 (Box 83)
    - Common Stock Circular for WILLINGHAM FINANCE COMPANY, 1952 (Box 83)
    - Blueprints for Offices & Studio WJBF, 1957 (Box 83)
    - Appraisal of an office building in Augusta, Georgia, 1965 (Box 83)
    - PRELIMINARY REPORT OF ORIGIN-DESTINATION TRAFFIC SURVEY AT AUGUSTA, GEORGIA 1957, 1959 (Box 83)
    - Structural Steel Specifications for Office sand Studio Building, WJBF-TV (Box 83)
    - IBM Folder - Correspondence, procedure guidelines, etc., 1962 (Box 83)
    - ALLEN B. DUMONT LABORATORIES Folder - Correspondence, informational pamphlets, Sales proposals, etc. regarding Sale/lease of transmitter from Allen B. Dumont Laboratories and an insurance claim after fire damaged the transmitter, 1952-1957 (Box 83)
    - DATA-VIEWING Folder - Publication clippings regarding Viewing statistics and assessment of these stats, 1954-1957 (Box 83)
    - DATA-MARKET Folder - Publication clippings regarding Demographics and markets in Georgia, 1960 (Box 83)
    - FILM (#2) (Prior to 1963) Folder - Correspondence, informational/promotional materials, etc. on programs purchased/considered by WJBF, 1960-1962 (Box 83)
    - General Precision Lab Folder - Correspondence, billing statement, etc. with company who dealt with WJBF and helped the station recover from fire, 1954- 1956 (Box 83)
    - General Electric Folder - Correspondence, contracts, etc. regarding Transmitting Antenna, 1957-1959 (Box 83)
    - Guild Films, Inc. Folder - Correspondences regarding business dealing with Guild Films Co., Inc., 1958-1960 (Box 83)
    - Hollywood TV Service Folder - Correspondences regarding dealings with Hollywood Television Service, 1955-1958 (Box 83)
    - Food & Drug Administration (T J Hennesy) Folder - Publication by/from the FDA, 1960-1962 (Box 83)
    - 1961 Folder - Correspondence to WJBF-TV regarding programming, mostly Thank you letters for helping with/through announcements (Box 83)
      KEY ITEM(S): LETTER FROM FUQUA TO GENERAL DWIGHT D. EISENHOWER, LETTER FROM STROM THURMOND TO NEWS DIRECTOR OF WJBF-TV, LETTER FROM MONITOR SOUTH regarding A PROGRAM THE STATION WAS TO AIR.
    - Atlantic Dealer News Vol. 10, No. 6 Nov. 1965 - Publication from The Atlantic Refining Co., 1965 (Box 83)
    - First Baptist Bulletin, Feb 24 1963 - Church newsletter announcing appearance by character from WJBF-TV, Trooper Terry, 1963 (Box 83)
    - VALUATION OF TV STATION WTVW EVANSVILLE, INDIANA, 1966 (Box 83)
    - 1959 Folder - Correspondence to WJBF-TV regarding programming, mostly thank you letters for helping with/through announcements, 1959 (Box 83)
      KEY ITEM: LETTER OF THANKS FROM STROM THRUMOND TO NEWS DIRECTOR OF WJBF-TV.
    - 1965 Folder - Correspondence to WJBF-TV regarding programming, mostly Thank you letters for helping with/through announcements (Box 84)
      KEY ITEM: LETTER OF THANKS FROM ARKANSAS REPRESENTATIVE TO FUQUA, LETTER FROM IRS regarding STATIONS HELP IN WAR ON MOONSHINE.
    - 1964 LETTERS OF APPRECIATION Folder - Correspondence to WJBF-TV regarding programming, mostly Thank you letters for helping with/through announcements (Box 84)
    - 1964 WOMAN'S WORLD FEB '64 - APRIL '65 Folder - lists of guests/features for Woman's World program, 1964 (Box 84)
    - 1964 EVENING EDITION FEB '64 - DEC. '64 Folder - lists of Evening Edition program interviewees, 1964 (Box 84)
    - TOP TEN DANCE PARTY FEB '64 - DEC. '64 Folder - lists of bands, interviewees, sites, etc. for program, 1964 (Box 84)
    - 1964 PUBLIC SERVICE Folder - lists of public service slots on WJBF-TV, 1964 (Box 84)
    - 1964 SPECIAL PROGRAMS '64 Folder - lists of special programs on WJBF-TV, 1964 (Box 84)
    - 1963 WJBF Folder - Correspondence to WJBF-TV regarding programming, mostly Thank you letters for helping with/through announcements, 1963 (Box 84)
    - 1963 - WJBF Folder - Assortment of materials (Thank you correspondences, Public Service Announcement lists, lists of program interviewees), 1963 (Box 84)
    - TV STATION - SALE #1 Folder - Correspondence, Balance Sheets, reports regarding potential purchase of TV stations, 1955-1965 (Box 84)
    - WJBF Binder - pages out of August 4, 1956, Augusta Herald, regarding Fire at WJBF Black and white photos of Fire damage, 1956 (Box 84)
    - 1962 WJBF Folder - Correspondence to WJBF-TV regarding programming, mostly Thank you letters for helping with/through announcements, 1962 (Box 84)
      KEY ITEM: LETTER OF THANKS FROM U.S. SENATOR HERMAN TALMADGE TO FUQUA.
    - Unidentified publication announcing sale of WNCT in Greenville, NC to Fuqua owned company, 1961 (Box 84)
    - PROCTOR & GAMBLE Folder - Correspondences between Proctor and Gamble and WJBF-TV, 1960-1962 (Box 84)
    - POLITICAL ADVERTISING Folder - Agreement Form and correspondences regarding political advertising on WJBF-TV, 1960-1965 (Box 85)
    - PRIZES Folder - Correspondence and brochures regarding prizes for use by WJBF-TV, 1960-1962 (Box 85)
    - MAXIMUM SERVICE TELECASTERS, INC. Folder - Bylaws, correspondence, and other materials pertinent to the Assoc. of Max Service Telecasters, 1956-1966 (Box 85)
    - Six different, unfoldered correspondences pertaining to the Georgia Association of Broadcasters, 1963-1964 (Box 85)
    - Response correspondence from T.J. Hennesy to Pvt. Alfred Gray regarding a program idea Gray pitched to Hennesy, 1962 (Box 85)
    - FCC Folder - Correspondence, publications, clippings, etc. regarding the FCC, 1958-1970 (Box 85)
    - GEORGIA-CAROLINA BROADCASTING CO Folder - Balance Sheet and other reports, Correspondences, legal/court documents, publication clippings, prospectus, etc., 1947-1963 (Box 85)
    - IDEAS Folder - Publication clippings, memos, correspondences, etc. regarding advertising ideas, 1955-1962 (Box 85)
    - WJBF - LICENSE RENEWALS Folder - publications, correspondences, forms to/from/regarding the FCC, 1961-1968 (Box 85)
    - L - MISCELLANEOUS Folder - Correspondences and forms regarding Gable Industries, Inc., 1972 (Box 85)
    - DECEMBER 5, 1966 NATCO BOARD OF DIRECTORS MEETING Folder - notes, correspondences, financial reports/spread sheets (Box 85)
    - NATCO - FUQUA INDUSTRIES, INC. BOARD MEETING - MONDAY, 2/13/67 Folder - Reports, notes, financial statements, brochure, 1966-1967 (Box 85)
    - RIGHT INVESTMENT CORP. Folder - Correspondence, Balance Sheet report, etc. regarding The Right Investment Corp, 1956-1969 (Box 86)
    - J.B. Fuqua - PLYWOOD PLANT Folder - Correspondence, inventories, advertisements, etc. regarding sale of Valdosta Plywood, 1966 (Box 86)
    - BURGER KING CORPORATION Folder - Leases, correspondence, closing statements, photographs, etc. regarding Burger King, 1966-1969 (Box 86)
    - J. B. Fuqua - NIGERIA Folder - Correspondences regarding possibility of setting up a clay products plant in Nigeria, 1966 (Box 86)
    - J. B. Fuqua - G&F Ry. (SOUTHERN) Folder - Correspondence, informational brochure, etc. regarding Georgia & Florida Railway Co., 1963-1967 (Box 86)
    - J.B.F. -WEST LAKE DEV. COMPANY Folder - Prospectus for The West Lake Development Co., 1966 (Box 86)
    - J. B. Fuqua - STUCKEY'S Folder - Balance Sheets, memos, statements of operations, correspondences, inventory audits, etc. regarding Stuckey's Pecans & Candies, 1963-1967 (Box 86)
    - J. B. Fuqua - PROPERTY Folder - Surveys and correspondences regarding various property ventures, 1963-1967 (Box 86)
    - Independent Television Corp. Folder - Correspondence with ITC regarding a disagreement about contract for Tugboat Annie program, 1958-1959 (Box 86)
    - Investment - 1963 Folder - Correspondences, informational brochures, etc. regarding search to acquire controlling interest in a manufacturing company (Box 86)
    - Announcement that Willingham Finance Co. is moving to a new location, including photograph of new site (Box 86)
    - INSURANCE - U. S. Guaranty Folder - Announcements, correspondences, news report script, etc. for a Life Insurance Company in which Fuqua owned stock, 1956-1957 (Box 86)
    - AMERICAN SHELL HOMES Folder - Financial Report, balance sheets, and correspondence regarding American Shell Homes, 1961-1962 (Box 86)
    - Model Homes Folder - Informational brochures and other materials regarding building/buying a house (Box 86)
    - McPhran Corp. Folder - Prospectus, Notice, and correspondence regarding the McPhran Corp., in which Fuqua invested, 1957-1961 (Box 86)
    - Assorted Financial Reports related to Claussen's, Inc., 1967 (Box 86)
    - FCC REQUEST FOR EXTENSION OF TIME to comment on matter of Expanded Use of UHF Television Channels, Docket No. 14229, 1961 (Box 86)
    - Correspondence from Radio Engineers A. D. Ring & Assoc. regarding FCC Case, Docket 14238, 1961 (Box 86)
    - CALCULATED LOSS OF SERVICE CAUSED BY SUGGESTED DROP-INS map from Radio Engineers A. D. Ring & Associates, 1960 (Box 86)
    - Correspondence from the Assoc. of Maximum Service Telecasters, Inc. regarding Proposal for Drop-ins, 1961 (Box 86)
    - Four (4) separate maps/Figures competing signals of station signals in Charlotte, NC area (Box 86)
    - Correspondence from Assoc. of Maximum Service Telecasters, Inc. to entire membership regarding hearing before the House Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committee, 1962 (Box 86)
    - FCC STATEMENT OF MST WITH RESPECT TO 'JOINT PETITION' OF WHNB-TV, ET AL., 1962 (Box 86)
    - FCC ORDER EXTENDING TIME FOR FILING REPLY COMMENTS, May 1962 (Box 86)
    - STATEMENT OF LESTER W. LINDOW EXECUTIVE DIRECTOR ASSOCIATION OF MAXIMUM SERVICE TELECASTERS, INC. BEFORE THE HOUSE COMMITTEE ON INTERSTATE AND FOREIGN COMMERCE (Box 86)
    - FCC ORDER EXTENDING TIME FOR FILING REPLY COMMENTS, March 1962 (Box 86)
    - Clipping from Broadcasting,February 26, 1962 (Box 86)
    - FCC REPLY COMMENTS OF ASSOCIATION OF MAXIMUM SERVICE TELECASTERS, INC., Docket No. 14229, 1962 (Box 86)
    - FCC ORDER EXTENDING TIME FOR FILING REPLY COMMENTS, July 1962 (Box 86)
    - FCC OPPOSITION AND COMMENTS OF ATLANTIC TELECASTING CORPORATION, Docket No. 14238, 1962 (Box 86)
    - Five (5) copies of FCC REPLY COMMENTS TO CHARLOTTE TELECASTERS, INC., Docket No. 14238, 1962 (Box 86)
    - FCC OPPOSITION COMMENTS AND ALTERNATIVE PROPOSAL, Docket No. 14238, 1962 (Box 86)
    - FCC REPLY COMMENTS OF CENTURY ADVERTISING COMPANY, Docket No. 14238, 1962 (Box 86)
    - FCC REPLY COMMENTS OF WATE, INC., Docket No. 14238, 1962 (Box 86)
    - FCC REPLY COMMENTS OF HAVENS & MARTIN, INC., Docket No. 14238, 1962 (Box 86)
    - Nine (9) copies of short form Audit of FUQUA INDUSTRIES, INC. AUGUSTA, GEORGIA JUNE 30, 1966 (Box 86)
    - Seven (7) copies of long form Audit of FUQUA INDUSTRIES, INC. AUGUSTA, GEORGIA JUNE 30, 1966 (Box 86)
      Cover letter included with these reports.
    - Eleven (11) copies of Balance Sheet report of CLAUSSENS, INC. AUGUSTA, GEORGIA JUNE 25, 1966 (Box 86)
    - Audit of KTVE, INC. JUNE 30, 1966 (Box 86)
      Cover letter included with this report.
    - Four (4) copies of Revised Balance Sheet report of CLAUSSENS, INC. AUGUSTA, GEORGIA JUNE 25, 1966 (Box 86)
    - Eight (8) copies of Audit for FUQUA INDUSTRIES, INC., AND SUBSIDIARIES JUNE 30, 1966 (Box 86)
    - Seven (7) copies of audit for GREAT LAKES INDUSTRIES, INC. JUNE 30, 1966 (Box 86)
    - WESTERN STONEWARE GENERAL Folder - balance sheet statements, Notes, correspondences, etc. regarding Western Stoneware, 1966-1967 (Box 87)
    - Balance sheet report for GEORGIA CAROLINA BROADCASTING COMPANY AUGUSTA, GEORGIA JUNE 30, 1960 (Box 87)
    - E. F. ELAM Folder - Assorted correspondence regarding Great Lakes Industries, 1967-1968 (Box 87)
    - Contract/agreement for Fuqua National, Inc. to buy Claussen's Inc., 1969 (Box 87)
    - Amendment of name to the State of Georgia charter to FUQUA NATIONAL, INC., 1967 (Box 87)
    - Two (2) Copies of Amendment of name of the State of Georgia charter to FUQUA INDUSTRIES, INC., 1963 (Box 87)
    - MATERIAL RELATED TO 1970-1973 WJBF FCC LICENSE Folder, 1970-1973 (Box 87)
    - Letter from Fuqua to Charles Call of Ward's Foods regarding potential merger, 1965 (Box 88)
    - FUQUA INDUSTRIES, INC. Folder - Biographical sketches, mailing lists, notes, description of companies, correspondence, publication clippings, 1966-1967 (Box 88)
    - POLARIS EVALUATION Envelope - Five (5) copies of NATCO VALUATION OF POLARIS ASSETS BEING ACQUIRED IN MERGER (Box 88)
    - LONE RANGER Envelope - Sixty-two (62) copies of The Mates Market Letter with article likening Fuqua to the Lone Ranger, 1966 (Box 88)
    - CONSOLIDATED EARNINGS - NOV Envelope - NATCO CORPORATION CONSOLIDATING FINANCIAL STATEMENTS NOVEMBER 30, 1966 (Box 88)